本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24
哈桑总统的卫队
President Hassan's security forces--
还在镇压反对派
they're still cracking down on the opposition
毫无缓和迹象
and they're not showing any signs of letting up.
谣言四起
The rumors have already started
说是作为签约国的英方打算退出和谈
that the British are pulling out as signatories to the accord.
召集各国代表
Assemble the representatives.
我亲自去请求他们让和谈继续
I want to appeal to them myself to stay the course.
其中一名嫌犯...
One of the suspects
与我们此次联合国的代表团成员有亲属关系
has family connections to a member of our delegation here at the UN.
哪个
Who?
贾莫特
Jamot.
你这是想拘捕我吗
Are you arresting me?
我要求和哈桑总统谈谈
I demand to speak with President Hassan.
这正是哈桑总统下的命令
President Hassan is the one who gave this order.
出什么事了  你声音不太对劲
What's wrong? You sound upset.
我想和你谈谈你的父亲
I need to speak with you about your father.
我得马上赶赴大使馆
I have to go to the embassy right now.
等我回来再私下见你
I'll meet you in private when I get back.
这里有证据保留室所在位置及其地形图
This has the address and schematic of the evidence lockup.
你用这张钥匙卡进去
This keycard will get you access.
我们怎么才能找到钱
How do we find the money?
证据存储箱都有编号
The evidence bins are numbered.
必须严格按我说的做  你就能自由进出了
Do exactly what I tell you to do, and you'll be in and out.
没人会知道你去过那里
No one will know you were there.
政府已经知道核原料的事了
The authorities know about the nuclear material.
带欧力格去诊所只会引狼入室
Putting Oleg in a clinic would lead them right to us.
不许看医生
No doctors.
医生说可以治好欧力格
The doctor said that Oleg could be treated.
他都告诉我方法了
He showed me how.
你翅膀硬了  敢质疑老子的判断力了吗
Who are you to question my judgment?
绝不要违抗老子的命令
Never disobey an order from your father.
对不住了  儿子
I'm sorry, my son.
告诉我买家的情况
Tell me about this buyer.
他叫恩斯特·迈尔
His name is Ernst Meier,
德国军火商
German arms dealer.
他想买什么货
What's he looking to buy?
武器级别的铀
Weapons-grade uranium.
我去会会这个叫迈尔的家伙
I'm going to have to meet this Meier,
为表诚意  他要先付定金
and I need a good-faith payment up front.
我不想重复说第二遍
I'm not going to tell you again.
出去  让我穿好衣服
Leave me alone and let me get dressed.
妈的  过来
Damn it, come here
否则交易就取消
or the deal's off.
你就是迈尔
Meier?
没错
That's right.
五百万在哪里
Where is the $5 million?
已经汇入你的账户了
The money is in your account.
放下武器  快  放下
Drop the weapon. Now! Drop it!
-迈尔  -你真以为能凭空卷走我五百万吗
- Meier. - You really think you can roll me for $5 million?
让我手下接电话
Let me talk to my man.
是我
Yes.
把他带回来
Bring him back here.
他想见你
He wants to see you.
以下事件发生在晚上十点至十一点
The following takes place between 10:00 P.M. and 11:00 P.M.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
进展很顺利
Well, that went well.
大家一致同意这份条约
Unanimous support for the treaty--
至少是几乎全体通过
well, nearly unanimous, anyway.
我心知肚明  自己快使尽浑身解数了
I have the distinct impression that I am running out of goodwill.
可能吧  可你为自己争取到了喘息的机会
Maybe, but you bought yourself some breathing room.
这些人已经错过了就寝时间
These people are already up past their bedtimes.
我想至少明早之前
I don't think we'll be hearing any more grousing
我们不会再听到任何怨言
until tomorrow morning at the earliest.
恭喜您  总统阁下
Congratulations, Madam President.
谢谢  很感谢您的支持
Thank you, I appreciated your support.
现在我希望您能告诉我事情的真相
Now I hope you'll explain to me what's really going on.
我想我已经说清楚了
I thought I did.
您召集了国家卫队
You invoked national security,
恕我直言  您还没给出解释
which, with respect, is not an explanation.
这只是在告诉我们别多管闲事
It's saying "Don't ask."
总统阁下
Madam President,
你我两国间基于相互信任
our countries have a unique relationship
近一个世纪以来  一直关系甚密
based on a trust developed over nearly a century now.
您告诉我的一切我绝对守口如瓶
Anything you say to me is in the strictest confidence.
您可以告诉贵国首相  但别告诉别人
You may tell your prime minister and no one else
哈桑总统此番镇压行动
that President Hassan's crackdown
不只是为他的自身安全考虑
isn't just a response to the attempt on his life.
有人在暗中买卖极度危险的核原料
There are unsecured nuclear materials in play.
显然他国家内部的反对派势力
Apparently a faction inside his country
被裁军计划搅得乱了阵脚
was so disturbed by the prospect of disarmament,
他们决定亲自出马
they decided to take matters into their own hands.
核原料在哪里
Where are the materials?
就在我国境内
Here on our soil.
反恐小组采取了卧底行动
CTU is running an undercover operation
此时此刻  正设法夺回核原料
to retrieve them as we speak.
谁的电话
Who is that?
我猜是我的后援
My guess is, it is my backup.
见到瓦德米尔前不许打电话
No calls till we get to Vladimir.
你看现在的形势轮得到你发号施令吗
Does this look like a situation where you get to make demands?
我是迈尔
It's Meier.
我看不见你了
I lost my sight line on you.
我正离开大楼
I'm leaving the building.
进展顺利吗
Everything okay?
钱已经汇入瓦德米尔的账户
The money's been transferred to Vladimir's account.
我们正要去他办公室
We're going to his office.
应该几分钟后就能到
We should be there in a few minutes.
我和后援队一起跟过去
I'll follow with a backup team.
可能没必要
That might not be necessary.
他们刚刚还大开杀戒
After what they just pulled,
你确定不要支援吗
you're sure you're comfortable without backup?
我还有其它考虑
There are other considerations.
你是指蕾妮还在他们手里
You mean they have Renee.
没错
That's right.
好吧  我们先按兵不动
Okay, we'll stay back.
我会告诉你进展
I'll let you know.
什么事
What was that?
告诉他什么进展
Let him know what?
闭嘴  只管开车
Shut up and drive.
好了  我通过电子眼看到他们了
Okay, I got 'em on traffic cam.
一切顺利吗
Is everything okay?
看来杰克掌握了主动权
Jack seems to be in control.
看来不错  一切尽在掌握
Looks fine, all things considered.
司机看起来心神不宁
Driver looks a little worried.
话说回来  那家伙是谁
Who is this guy anyway?
我该对他做个脸部识别吗
Should I pass him on to facial recognition?
丹娜
Dana?
我得接个电话
I've got to take this.
是啊  没什么大不了
Yeah, sure, no biggie.
只不过是极度危险的核原料而已
Just unsecured nuclear materials.
喂
Yes.
我们到了  就在证物储存大楼外
We're there, outside the evidence building.
你在旁边小巷是吗
You're in the side alley, right?
不是
No,
我们把车停在前面  这样就能引人注意
we parked out front so everyone can see us.
得了吧  你以为我是蠢材吗
Come on, what do you think I am?
好  我一步步教你做
Okay, look, I need to walk you through this step by step.
我知道  我们准备好了
I know, we're ready.
我这里出了点状况  你等我几分钟
Well, something just came up here and I need you to hang on for a few minutes.
原地等吗  我们会被发现的  珍妮
Here? We're kind of exposed, Jenny.
如果你继续待在那  就没事了
You'll be fine if you just stay still.
距离下次巡逻还需要三十分钟
We have a 30-minute window before the next security pass.
我会尽快回来帮你
I will be with you the second I can.
阿洛  黑斯廷斯要我们去他办公室
Arlo, Hastings wants us in his office
了解最新外勤动态
for a field update.
问个假设性的问题可以吗
Can I ask you a hypothetical question?
如果是丹娜的问题  就不用假设了
If it's about Dana, it's not hypothetical.
如果你未婚妻搞外遇
If your fiancee was cheating on you,
你会想知道吗
would you want to know?
如果是假设的话  那要看是谁问的
Hypothetically, who'd be asking--
是某位不想要饭碗了的偷窥狂在问吗
some creepy stalker who's about to get fired?
我是认真的
I'm serious.
我也是  上楼去吧
So am I. Just go upstairs.
这不关你的事
It's none of your business.
丹娜  科尔刚刚和杰克通了电话
Dana, Cole just called about Jack.
黑斯廷斯要我们去他办公室
Hastings wants us in his office.
把钥匙给我
Pass me back the keys.
慢慢地出来
Slowly get out,
把手放到车顶上
put your hands on the roof.
我们走
Let's go.
你就是这么谈生意的吗
So this is how you do business?
我如约预付了你五百万
I wire you the $5 million like we agreed,
然后你就想把我干掉
and then you try and take me out.
我没想到你是真的想做这笔生意
I did not think you were for real.
一场误会而已
It was a misunderstanding,
但都过去了
but it's past.
不打不相识
We are here.
瓦德米尔已开始跟他的老主顾们联络了
Vladimir has already started calling his contacts,
而且询问了对方关于核原料的事
inquiring about the nuclear materials.
我不在乎他做了什么
I don't care what he's done.
我要跟你谈谈
I want to talk to you.
那就说吧
So talk.
我要跟我的搭档单独谈谈  就现在
I want to talk to my partner alone now.
听着  他现在很生气
Look, he's upset,
人之常情
understandably.
机不可失
This is our chance.
我们应该现在就把他干掉
We should take him out now.
不行  我们需要他完成这次交易
No, we need him to do this deal.
为一个臭婊子值得冒这个险吗
Don't risk everything for a whore.
你要是再敢这么说她
You ever talk about her like that again,
我就把你做了
I'll kill you.
听明白了吗
You understand?
你到底在干嘛
What the hell are you doing?
我被授权让你退出行动
I have authorization to pull you out.
不  这是不可能的
No, that's not possible.
蕾妮  你已帮了大忙  下面的任务交给我
Renee, you've taken us this far, I'm going to finish it.
杰克  你不能这么做  首先他不信任你
Jack, you can't. He doesn't trust you, first of all.
他愿意继续交易的唯一原因是因为我
The only reason he's agreeing to continue this is me.
我很好  真的
I'm fine, really.
你要打电话吗  那我们走吧
You want to make calls, let's go.
在这点上你没有发言权
You don't have a say in this.
-我要让你退出行动  -不行  听着
- I am pulling you out. - No, look,
还没你想的那么糟
it's not a big deal.
我知道六年前他都对你做了些什么
I know what he did to you six years ago,
并且事情也已经不那么简单了
and it is a big deal.
杰克  如果我们就这样结束行动
Jack, if we stop this now,
那我所做的一切努力都白费了
then everything that I have done is for nothing.
没时间了
We're running out of time.
我们走
Let's go.
我们都快成功了  这么做是值得的
We're almost there, it'll be worth it.
翻译：非燕   hodala   我是无辜的   wdjmhs   罗玉凤   叶eve
■
时间轴：钉子    馬姑娘     校对：何何    我是无辜的    金翠    Nil
后期：冰河     监制：何何   冰卡   拾六
■
卡文  听到了吗
Kevin, are you there?
是的
Yeah.
我以为你把我们忘了
I thought you forgot about us.
我倒希望如此
I wish I could.
拜托  别那个样子
Come on, don't be like that.
我们能开始了吗
Are we good to go?
对  马上开始
Yes, move now.
我们走
Let's go.
门边上有个门禁装置  用我给你的那张卡
There's a security panel next to the door. Use the keycard I gave you.
密码是1668
The code is 1668.
1668.
继续走  警报声一会就会停掉
Keep moving, it will stop in a second.
如果你想得到那十二万
If you want the $120,000
你必须在二十分钟内脱身
you will be out of there in less than 20 minutes.
好的  哪扇门
Okay, which door is it?
左边最后一扇  密码是4660
It's the last one on the left. The code is 4660.
这有点像揭开圣诞节上做的倒计时链
It's like Christmas... with chain link.
好了  我们怎么才能找到钱
Okay, how do we find the money?
就在3101号隔间里
It's in section 3101.
-3101  -过道到底后靠左手边
- 3101. - It's down the aisle on your left.
-3101  -密码是2824
- 3101. - The code is 2824.
靠左手边最后一间
The last one on the left.
3101  你看见了吗
3101-- do you see it?
对  就在这里
Yeah, right here.
怎么回事  哥们
What the hell, man?
珍妮  怎么进不去
Jen, what the hell is going on?
号码是多少
What number is it?
是3101吗
Is it 3101?
3101  这间是3110  拜托
3101-- this is 3110. Come on.
你们怎么回事
What is wrong with you two?
搞错了不行吗  别说了
Hey, it's called a mistake, all right? Back off.
那么到底在哪里
So where is it?
过道走到底左手边就是3101
3101 is down the aisle on the left.
-走到底  走到底  -密码是2824
- Down here, down here. - The code is 2824.
2824  2824  2824
2824, 2824, 2824.
证物箱编码是4301
Bin number's 4301.
4301.
伙计  全是数字
Oh, man, it's too many numbers.
4301  4301
4301, 4301.
找到了
Got it!
太棒了  伙计
That's beautiful, man.
太棒了
That's beautiful.
别说了  赶快出去
Just shut up and get out of there.
不到十五分钟就会有人来巡岗了
The next patrol is in less than 15 minutes.
你拿到钱了
You've got the money.
赶紧把门关上然后闪人
Close the doors and leave.
十五分钟  我们这就走
15 minutes. We're leaving.
脱身后打我电话
Call me when you're clear.
一定  珍妮
I sure will, Jenny.
我们走吧
Let's go!
再等等
Not yet.
看看还有别的什么
Check out some of this stuff.
说真的  走吧  伙计  巡逻的人要来了
Hey, seriously, come on, man. Patrol's on its way.
是啊  十五分钟后才来
Yeah, 15 minutes.
你确定吗
Are you sure, then?
没听说有人在卖这种核原料吗
You haven't heard of anyone dealing in these materials?
好吧  感谢你百忙中听我的电话
All right. Well, thank you for your time.
很抱歉  打扰你了
I'm sorry to trouble you.
一无所获
Nothing.
他们不喜欢这么晚了还被电话骚扰
They did not appreciate being called so late.
蕾妮  给我切点面包
Renee, cut me some bread.
给
Here.
喝点水可能会让你轻松点
You might want to ease up on the drinking.
你已经打了好几个电话了
You've got some calls to make.
我想喝就喝
I drink what I want.
蕾妮  面包呢
Renee, where's the bread?
来了
Coming.
喝吧
Drink.
怎么切得
What is this?
太薄了
It is too thin.
应该再切得厚点
It should be thick.
又厚又漂亮
Nice and thick.
这就对了
There we are.
你知道吗  她变了
She's changed, you know?
六年前
Six years ago,
她觉得我配不上她
she thought she was too good for me.
现在她听话多了
Now, she is much more friendly.
也许我该谢谢你
Maybe I should thank you--
全拜你们在墨西哥城一起度过的时光所赐
all that time you were together in Mexico City.
拜托
Come on.
我看见你瞧她的眼神了
I see how you look at her.
别告诉我  你对她没意思
Don't tell me you didn't.
想唠叨的话  快去打电话
You want to keep talking, do it on the phone.
要不然核原料会被别人买走
Otherwise, the nuclear materials will be gone,
我们的交易就吹了
and this deal will be dead.
好吧  可我不喜欢你在这里咄咄逼人的架势
Fine, but I don't like you breathing down my neck.
卢戈  把他带出去
Lugo, get him out of here.
我的伏特加喝完了
And I'm running out of my vodka.
去给我买点
Go get me some more.
坐下
Sit down.
去把守前门
我去去就回
I won't be long.
我的小儿子
My younger son.
我想葬了他  格雷戈神父
I wanted to bury him, Father Gregor.
当然  可要等等
Of course, but that will take a little time.
墓地的工人得把坟墓准备好
The cemetery workers need to prepare the grave...
不行  现在就葬
No. You will do it now
就葬在后面
out back.
我的人会帮他挖坟墓
My men will dig his grave.
瑟吉·彼得罗维奇
Sergei Petrovich,
那你就按正确的做法来
Then make it right.
把他当做一位战死沙场  马革裹尸的战士
Treat him like a soldier who died on the battlefield and must be buried there.
他是死在...
Is that how he died?
沙场上吗
In battle?
你按标准来就行了
You just make it right.
说完所有祷告词
Say all the prayers.
我的身后事  我不在乎
Where I end up, I don't care.
可这孩子  是与天使同在的
But this boy is with the angels.
我的人很快就来
My men will be with you soon.
回避一下
Leave us.
起来
Get up.
看看我  约瑟夫
Look at me, Josef.
我想让你明白
I want you to understand
我所做的一切  都是为了你
that everything I've done, I've done for you
都是为了家族
and for our family.
您杀了我弟弟
You killed my brother.
因为我爱他
Because I loved him,
因为我不忍心看他活受罪
because I couldn't bear to see him suffer,
也因为别无选择
because there was no other way.
总有其他办法的
There's always another way.
面对核原料的买卖时  我们别无选择
Not when we are dealing with nuclear materials.
我们不能冒被政府发现的危险
We cannot risk the authorities finding out.
你知道的
You know that.
你不明白我为什么干这行吗
You don't know why I'm doing this?
因为我死后
Because when I die,
我想给你  给家族留下一笔巨大的遗产
I want to leave you and your family a worthy inheritance.
财富  名望
Wealth, respect,
影响力
consequence.
你能明白吗
Can you understand that?
终有一天你会明白的
One day you will.
你儿子长大后  你就会明白
As your son grows older, you will.
你也会明白
And you will understand
我是多么爱你
how much I love you.
我唯一的儿子
My only son.
格雷戈神父过来安葬欧力格
Father Gregor is here to bury Oleg.
你去帮他吗
Will you help him?
他是我弟弟
He's my brother.
谢谢你
Thank you.
准备好了告诉我
Call when you are ready.
怎么了
What is it?
是瓦德米尔·勒塔纳的电话
Vladimir Laitanan.
他说事关重大
He says it's important.
瓦德米尔  有何贵干
Vladimir, what do you want?
瑟吉·彼得罗维奇
Sergei Petrovich.
抱歉突然来电打扰  先生
I apologize for calling you out of the blue like this, sir.
你家人还好吗
Uh, your family is well?
我问你有何贵干
I said, what do you want?
我有笔生意跟你谈
I have a business proposition.
那工作时间再打给我  别半夜三更地打来
Then call me in business time, not in the middle of the night.
不  不是  这件事等不得
No, no, no, this can't wait.
我听说有核原料要卖
I hear there are materials for sale,
很贵很危险的那种
expensive materials, dangerous ones.
少跟我拐弯抹角  什么原料
Talk straight. What materials?
核原料棒
Nuclear rods.
高浓缩铀
Highly enriched uranium.
那你为什么打给我
So, why are you calling me?
如果有谁有本事做成这种买卖  那一定是你
If anyone has the organization to pull off such a deal, it's you.
过奖了
I'm flattered.
我有个买家  一个德国人
I have a buyer here, a German.
他愿意出一大笔钱
He's willing to pay a great deal of money for them.
任何人出价的两倍
Double any offer you have.
那他就跟你一样蠢
Then he is as stupid as you are.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
没人敢贩卖核原料棒  没人敢
Nobody deals in nuclear rods, nobody.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
误会了
A misunderstanding.
别再打给我
Don't call me again.
他不知道我说的什么
He had no idea what I was talking about.
好吧  那我们打给下一个
All right, then we call the next person.
你没听明白
You're not listening.
他说没人敢贩卖这些东西
He says nobody sells these things.
你就要做成人生中最大的买卖了  瓦德米尔
You're close to the biggest deal of your life, Vladimir.
他只是嫉妒  他不能参与其中
He's just jealous that he's not in on it.
过来  过来
Come here. Come here.
喂  等等
Look, later.
等等
Later.
你再打点电话
Once you've made more calls.
拜托
Come on.
好吧  好吧
Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
瓦德米尔知道浓缩铀棒的事了
Vladimir Laitanan knows about the fuel rods.
你打算怎么做
What are you going to do?
我是巴扎耶夫  你得停下来
你知道该去哪
这样我们就迟了
照做  等我电话
安东
Anton?
安东  靠路边停车
我们不做了
喂
Yes?
总统阁下  我是艾莉森·泰勒
Mr. President, it's Allison Taylor.
我们定好继续协商的
We were scheduled to resume our discussions.
我知道我迟到了  抱歉
I'm late, I know. I apologize.
今晚的事...
The events of this evening...
今晚的事非同小可
The events of this evening make it more important than ever
我们要完成协议
that we complete our work on this treaty.
总统阁下  我要明确您的意图
Mr. President, I need to know your intentions.
我的意图
My intentions?
您对国内的镇压
The crackdown on your countrymen.
我听说  您连一位自己的幕僚都逮捕了
I've been informed that you've even arrested one of your own delegation.
那是我们的内政
That's an internal matter.
不  阁下  没那么简单
No, sir, it is not.
不到一个小时前
Less than an hour ago,
我跟二十几个国家代表保证
I assured delegates from two dozen countries
您还是我们实现和平的最佳人选
that you were still our best hope for peace.
我个人跟他们担保  您会遵守
I personally guaranteed them you'd observe
我们签署的协议及其精神
the letter and spirit of this agreement we're signing.
我会的
And I will.
您能向我保证吗
Do I have your word on that?
总统阁下  未来几小时内
Madame President, within the next few hours,
抓捕行动将会停止
the arrests will stop.
对此我将采取必要措施
I'm taking measures to assure that.
那被您逮捕的那位代表呢
And the delegate you've taken into custody?
会被释放或被指控
Will be released or charged.
我向您保证
You have my word.
谢谢
Thank you.
他的口气如何
How do you think he sounded?
不像他自己
Not like himself.
他招了吗
Did he talk?
没有  阁下
No, sir.
贾莫特拒不承认对针对您的阴谋知情
Jamot denies all knowledge of the plot against you.
审讯得严吗
How forceful was the interrogation?
很严
Very.
我亲自审的
I did it myself.
我不相信他同您弟弟有任何瓜葛
I don't believe he's involved with your brother in any way.
你知道贾莫特跟极端分子有亲属关系
You know Jamot has connections with the extremists.
一个反对党的表亲  阁下
A cousin in the opposition party, sir.
仅此而已
That's all.
他要是不招  我们就得来点硬的了
If he won't talk, we have to force the issue.
他家中有妻小  对吧
He has a wife and children back home, is that correct?
一个九岁的儿子和一个七岁的女儿
A boy, nine. A girl, seven.
让安全局逮捕他们
Have the Security Services arrest them.
使用任何必要的压力迫使贾莫特招供
Apply whatever pressure's necessary to make Jamot talk.
你有话要说吗
You have something to say?
是的  阁下
Yes, sir.
我有
I do.
您将我们团结起来
You rallied us around you on the promise
承诺不再使用暴力手段
that you would put an end to such tactics.
总统阁下  我会尽一切努力
Mr. President, I will do everything humanly possible
找到您弟弟的下落  但是我请求您
to find your brother but, please,
别逼我违背你我共同坚持的原则
do not ask me to violate the principles that you and I both stand for.
谢谢  塔林
Thank you, Tarin.
我妻子走了
With my wife gone,
再也没人跟我说真心话了
I have no one to speak the truth to me anymore.
再检查一遍所有人的电脑和电话记录
Check everyone's computer and phone records again.
务必不要遗漏任何蛛丝马迹
See to it that nothing was overlooked.
当然  阁下
Of course, sir.
我们走
Let's go.
纳比尔留在这里收拾这些文件
Nabeel can stay and pack up these files.
别管这些文件了
Forget the files.
什么
Sir?
给安全局打电话
Call the Security Services
让他们照我的命令把贾莫特的妻小抓起来
and have them round up Jamot's wife and children as I asked.
我不明白  您刚告诉塔林...
I don't understand. You just told Tarin that...
我直接命令你
I gave you a direct order.
你执行还是不执行
You obey it or not?
遵命  阁下
Yes, sir.
我这就给安全局打电话
I will call Security Services.
好
Good.
把塔林的材料从这里找出来
And find Tarin's records in that mess.
他不想让贾莫特招供  可能另有企图
He might have his own reasons for not wanting Jamot to talk.
尼克
Nick.
尼克  赶快  我们得赶紧走了
Nick, come on, we've got to move, man.
巡警随时可能出现
There's going to be a patrol here any minute.
赶快
Come on.
-把钱给我  -什么
- Give me the money. - What?
钱  蠢货
The money, dumbass!
这些钱我们五五分账
We're going to split this.
我不会再重复一遍
I ain't gonna ask you again.
你跟我玩真的吗
You can't be serious.
混蛋  别闹了
Bitch! Knock it off!
赶快  伙计  快走
Come on, man, let's go!
混球
Jackass!
我说过我们早该离开
I told you we should've gone!
真是个白痴
Such an idiot.
我刚接到汉密尔顿堡危险品实验室的来电
I just received a call from the Hazmat Lab at Fort Hamilton.
他们分析了从刺客身上发现的铀残留物
They've analyzed the traces of uranium found on Hassan's assassin.
他们认定了铀的来源了吗
Did they identify where it came from?
样本太小了  没法精确判明
Sample's too small to be precise,
但是那些铀来自前苏联地区
but the uranium is of Soviet origin.
他们正重新校正检测结果
They're recalibrating their tests now.
很好  随时向我汇报  克洛伊
Great. Keep me informed, Chloe.
卡文  你们出来了吗
Kevin, are you out of there?
不  还没有
No, not exactly.
你们怎么回事
What are you talking about?
你说你们二十分钟前就离开了
You told me you left there 20 minutes ago.
好吧  可是我们没出来  现在有人进来了
Okay, yeah, we didn't. Okay, now somebody's here.
你个白痴
You idiot!
我承认我白痴行吧  赶快帮忙
Yeah, fine, all right, just hurry.
有人进入走廊了
Somebody's in the hallway.
难以置信  你竟捅出这种娄子
I can't believe you let this happen.
你要是被抓  我就死定了
If you get caught, I am dead.
我们是一根线上的蚂蚱
Hey, we all are.
好吧  赶快想想办法把我们弄出去
All right, so just find us a way out of here.
坚持一下
Hang on.
别慌
Stay calm.
是个警察
It's a cop.
他就在你们进去的房间外边的走廊里
He's in the hallway right outside the room you're in.
还有另外一个出口
There's another exit.
就在你身后的拐角
In the corner right behind you.
快  快  快
Come on, come on! Come on.
天哪  你... 你们都干了些什么
My God, wh-what have you done?
见鬼  锁着呢
Damn it! It's locked!
他马上就要进来了
He's coming inside right now.
你们得从他背后溜过去
You're going to have to slip past him,
从你们进来的门出去
go out the door you came in.
总台  我是10岗11号  我在仓库...
Control, this is ten post 11. I'm at the warehouse...
尼克
Nick!
你在干什么  不要
What are you doing?! No!
卡文  拦住他
Kevin, stop him!
快走  快走  快走
Come on, come on, come on.
他已经报警了
Hey! He called it in.
我们得赶紧走
We gotta go!
快
Come on!
-卡文  拦住他  -快走
-Kevin, stop him! - Come on.
我们脱身后马上给你打电话
We'll call you when we're clear!
塔林  你还好吧
Tarin, are you all right?
你什么时候从大使馆回来的
When did you get back from the embassy?
刚回来
Just now.
我能进来吗
May I come in?
怎么了
What is it?
这里就我一个人
It's only me here.
这里安全
It's safe.
出什么事了
What's wrong?
你知道你父亲抓了很多人
You know your father has had many people arrested,
包括贾莫特
including Jamot.
现在又把贾莫特的妻子和两个孩子关在家里
Now he's having Jamot's wife and two children detained back home,
以此来逼他招供
so they can be used to force him to talk.
不会的
No.
这里面一定有误会
There must be some mistake.
他亲自下的命令
He gave the order himself.
我本以为我已经说服他了
I thought I'd convinced him not to,
但是他骗了我
but he was lying to me,
背着我下了命令
he went behind my back.
凯拉  你父亲是位伟人
Kayla, your father is a great man.
我崇敬他胜过任何人
I respect him more than anyone I have ever known.
但法哈德的背叛改变了他
But Farhad's betrayal has changed him.
我们能做什么
What can we do?
请开门
Open up, please.
他们来这里干什么
What are they doing here?
我不知道
I don't know.
开门
Open up.
塔林  待在这里
Tarin, stay here.
-什么事  纳比尔  -凯拉小姐
- Yes, Nabeel? - Miss Kayla,
我们到处在找塔林
we've been looking everywhere for Tarin.
您看见他了吗
Have you seen him?
没有
No.
出什么事了吗
Is there some problem?
你以为你在做什么
What do you think you're doing?
我们奉命行事  凯拉小姐
We have orders, Miss Kayla.
我说了他不在这里
I said he wasn't here.
很抱歉  但是我不相信
I'm sorry, but I don't believe you.
你不能就这么硬闯进来
You can't just barge in here!
我要跟我父亲谈谈
I need to talk to my father!
纳比尔
Nabeel.
你何必带着荷枪实弹的警卫来找我
Why do you need armed guards to come looking for me?
总统说你可能跟他的弟弟是一伙的
The president says you may be involved with his brother.
凭什么这么说
Based on what?
无凭无据
Nothing.
就因为我不允许折磨一个无辜的家庭吗
Only that I would not allow an innocent family to be tortured.
他命令我拘禁你
He's ordered me to detain you.
我别无选择
I have no choice.
你当然有选择的余地  纳比尔
You do have a choice, Nabeel.
告诉我父亲他犯了一个错误
Tell my father he's made a mistake,
没有人比塔林更忠心耿耿了
that there's no one more loyal than Tarin.
纳比尔  这太荒唐了  你知道的
Nabeel, this is insane, and you know it.
别自讨苦吃  好吗
Don't make this worse, please.
你们没看出来吗  我也束手无策
Don't you see? My hands are tied.
让我去跟我父亲谈谈
Let me talk to my father.
他下令不允许有人打搅
He's given orders not to be disturbed.
您也不行
Even by you.
我会跟他谈谈的
I'll talk to him!
我会让他回心转意的
I'll get him to change his mind!
不  我明白  罗曼
No, I understand, Roman.
我们以后有机会再合作  好吗
We'll do business some other time, okay.
就这样了
That's it.
最后一个
Last one.
他也不知道核原料棒的事
He also knows nothing about nuclear rods.
他也说做这个买卖等于自杀
He also said it's suicide to deal in them.
迈尔在浪费我们的时间
Meier has wasted our time.
不  迈尔的情报很准确  我们得再想想
No, look, Meier's intel is good. So we need to think.
-还能打给谁  -没人了
- Who else can we call? - No one.
我已给所有可能做这种生意的人打过电话了
I've called everyone who could possibly deal in these things.
那就是你打过电话的这些人里有了解情况的
Then somebody that you've already talked to has to know something.
蕾妮  到此为止吧
Renee, it's-it's done.
可能他们不想承认知情
Look, maybe they don't want to admit it.
或者他们不知道你对这件事有多重视
Maybe they don't know how serious you are.
-你应该再给他们打回去  -我说了不行
- You should call them back. - I said no.
告诉他们你有买主  告诉他们你有钱付款
Tell them that you have the buyer, tell them you have the money.
闭嘴
Shut up!
我喜欢你的脸蛋不代表
Just because I like your face doesn't mean
我能忍受你胡说八道
I have to put up with your crap.
我们一个晚上就赚到了五百万
We made $5 million. A good night's work.
为什么我们放着十倍的钱不赚
Why settle for five when we can have 50?
你什么时候变得这么贪得无厌了
When did you get so greedy?
五百万足够了
$5 million is plenty.
加上成全了我们一对野鸳鸯  也不算糟吧
Plus we have each other, that's not too bad, is it?
不算糟
Oh, it's not bad.
但是可以更好
But it could be better.
再给他们打一遍
Call them again.
就当为了我
Do it for me.
快  瓦德米尔  再催催他们
Come on, Vladimir, push them harder.
-没有不透风的墙  -你到底哪根筋不对
- Somebody knows something. - What is your problem?
没人知道了  该打的电话都打完了
Nobody knows. There's no one left to call.
你现在就出去  告诉迈尔他可以走了
Now you go out there and you tell Meier to leave, okay.
我不会去告诉他
I'm not telling him anything!
除非你继续打电话  否则我不去
Not until you try again.
听着  一切都结束了  你有病啊
Look, it's over! What is wrong with you?!
我需要这桩买卖
I need this deal.
这就是你来的目的吗  就为买卖
That is why you're here? The deal?
不然还有什么理由  你觉得我是为你而来的吗
Why else? Do you think that I'm here for you?
站起来
Get up.
住手  住手
Stop! Stop!
住手
Stop!
天哪
Oh, God.
Oh, God!
没事了  没事了
It's all right. It's all right.
都结束了
It's over.
结束了  没事了
It's over. It's okay.
勒塔纳联系了
Laitanan contacted everyone
所有他认为可能会有核原料消息的卖家
he thought might have information on the nuclear materials.
没有人回应
No one responded.
然后他说该做的都做了
That's when he said he was finished.
蕾妮一直在给他施压
Renee kept pushing him,
然后事态就失控了
and it got ugly.
勒塔纳死了
Laitanan's dead.
他先袭击了她
He attacked her.
然后呢  你就干掉了他吗
And so, what, you took him out?
不  是她干的
No, she did.
她干的
She did?
半小时以前
Half an hour earlier,
她还在和这家伙风流快活
she was having sex with the guy.
这到底是怎么回事  杰克
How does that even happen, Jack?
怎么  她失控了吗
What, she lose it?
她只是自卫而已
She was defending herself.
在跟进这案子前  你我都知道他有暴力倾向
Look, we knew this guy was violent before we even went in.
他有暴力倾向吗
He's violent?
-他都死翘翘了  -是的
- He's dead on the floor. - Yes, he is.
现在我们仍没解除核原料的威胁
And right, now, we still don't have the nuclear materials secured,
所以我建议另找线索
so I suggest we move on.
另找线索
Move on?
他是我们唯一的线索  杰克
He was our only lead, Jack.
现在你叫我上哪找新线索
Now, where do we move on to?
可以从勒塔纳打出的电话着手调查
We can start by working the phone calls that Laitanan made.
这里也有一些文件
There's also physical files here
以及一台电脑可供调查
and a computer to go through.
好吧  科尔  你听到了吗
Yeah, fine. Cole, are you getting this?
是的  长官  我们正在路上
Yes, sir. We're en route
刚从集结待命区出发  五分钟后到
from the staging area, five minutes out.
还需要鉴证科来现场取样调查
We're gonna need forensics to rip this place apart.
好  班尼特跟我一起来了
Yeah, I got Bennett with me.
在大部队赶来之前  他可以先来协助
He can coordinate till the full team arrives.
尽你们所能吧
Just do what you can.
把勒塔纳的尸体带回来进行尸检
And bring Laitanan's body back here for autopsy.
我想知道到底发生了什么
I want to know what the hell happened.
有什么别的好消息吗
Any other good news?
杰克
Jack?
科尔
Cole?
丹娜
Dana?
什么事
Excuse me?
我说还有别的什么新进展吗
I said, anything else?
没有  长官
No, sir.
好吧
Okay, then.
-你们来了再说吧  -是  长官
- We'll see you when you get here. - Yes, sir.
我们整个行动都给搞砸了
Our entire operation just went south.
你能稍稍精力集中一点吗
You think you could show a little interest?
给我打起精神来
Pull it together!
你没必要这样做
You didn't have to do that.
做什么
Do what?
就是在黑斯廷斯面前给我打掩护
Cover for me with Hastings.
我说的都是实话
All I did was tell him the truth.
他们看到瓦德米尔尸体时  就会真相大白
When they see Vladimir, they'll know what happened.
你认为真相是什么
What do you think happened?
正如你所说
It's like you said.
我还没准备好
I couldn't handle it.
我很抱歉
God, I'm sorry.
没关系的
It's all right.
不  有关系
No, it's not.
我刚才差点杀了你
I could have killed you.
我是成事不足败事有余
I've made such a mess of everything.
我本以为如果我能完成这次任务的话
I just thought that if... if I did this,
我就能恢复正常
I could make it all right.
就能找回我原来的生活
I could have my life back.
你随时都能找回你原来的生活
You can have your life back any time you want.
只要你有这样的愿望
You just need to want it.
怎么找回
How?
我试过了  根本不知道如何找回
I've tried, and I don't know how.
我...
I don't...
我一无所有  无依无靠
I don't have anything, anyone.
你还有我
You've got me.
知道吗
Okay.
看着我  看着我
Look at me. Look at me.
知道吗
Okay?
我不想像这样结束
I didn't want it to end like this.
我明白
I know.
我们的行动已经比三小时前推进了很多
Look, we're a lot farther ahead than we were three hours ago.
勒塔纳打过的每个电话都是我们能跟进的重要线索
Every call Laitanan made is a solid lead that we can follow up,
这都归功于你
and that's because of you.
你完成了你的使命
You did your part.
现在就让反恐小组接手吧
Now let CTU do their job.
好吗
Please?
让我送你回家
Let me take you home.
好
Okay.
那就好
该死  他们刚才就一定已经出发了
Damn it, they really must have been moving.
反恐小组准该赶到这里了
CTU's here already.
听我说  这很重要
Listen to me. This is really important.
瓦德米尔先攻击你  你是自卫
Vladimir attacked you, and you defended yourself.
-事情就是这样  -要这样说吗
- That's what happened. - I don't know.
我作证  如果有其他任何人要质疑这一点
I do, and if anybody else wants to ask you questions about that,
我会和你站在一起回答他们
I'll be right there with you to answer them.
我知道了
Okay.
让我先去跟他们碰一下头
Let me go talk to them.
是俄国人
They're Russian.
瓦德米尔肯定联系到了有浓缩铀棒的人
Vladimir must have contacted whoever's got the rods.
他们只是不想让他知道
They just didn't want him to know.
这个耳机你拿着
Hold on to this.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
我要让他们带我走
I need to let them take me.
不  我们得离开这里
No. We have to get out of here.
听我说  你想要你之前的努力付诸东流吗
Listen to me. You want everything you've done so far to matter?
我必须这样做
I need to do this.
等反恐小组一到
When CTU gets here,
你叫他们用无人机追踪我
you tell them to start tracking me from the air.
我们就借这些人顺藤摸瓜
These people are gonna lead us to everything we're looking for.
他们会杀了你的
They will kill you.
不会  最多被严刑逼供
No. At worst, they're going to have to vet me,
看看我知道多少
find out how much I know.
但这会给我们争取足够的时间
It should buy us enough time.
躲在这里
Hide in here.
拿着这个
Take this.
如果有人开门  你就开枪
If this door opens again, you start shooting.
这里出什么事了
有三具尸体
这他妈的是什么鬼东西
别开枪
Don't shoot!
Please!
我会打开门
I'm opening the door.
我没有武器
I'm unarmed.
看到吗  两手都是空的
See? Both my hands.
看到吗  都没有  我没有武器
See? No problem. I'm unarmed.
别开枪
Don't shoot.
这里发生了什么
What happened here?
发生了什么
What happened?!
他们想黑吃黑
They tried to rip me off.
但你们和我  我们可以做笔买卖
But you and I-- we can do business.
不  别开枪
No! Don' shoot.
如果你杀了我
If you kill me,
你会让你老板损失一大笔钱
you're gonna cost your boss a lot of money.
还有其他人和你一起吗
Who else is with you here?
没有  所有人都死了
No one. Everybody else is dead.
我只想做生意
All I want to do is business.
带他走
米哈伊尔
Mikhail!
我们走
来了
汉森  上传到反恐小组
Hansen, upload to CTU.
黑斯廷斯长官
Mr. Hastings,
现场安全  您马上能看到现场视频
site is secure,  video's coming through.
三具尸体  你们看到了吗
Three bodies. Are you getting this?
是的  我们看到了
Yes,  we are.
发现杰克和蕾妮的踪迹吗
Any sign of Jack or Renee?
没有  长官
No, sir.
我在这里
I'm here.
这里
Here.
是蕾妮  长官  她还活着
It's Renee, sir. She's alive.
蕾妮  杰克在哪里
Renee, where's Jack?
俄国人把他带走了
The Russians took him.
就是那些手上持有核原料的人
The ones that have the nuclear materials.
怎么走的  我们一直在监视这幢楼
How? We've been monitoring the building.
没有车辆离开过这地方
No vehicles left this area.
我不... 我不知道
I don't... I don't know.
当时他们突然出现  怎么会...
They just suddenly appeared, but...
等等  是杰克让他们把他带走的
Wait. Jack let himself be taken.
他说你们会用无人机追踪他
He said that you'd be monitoring him from the air.
我们没有发现任何异常
We haven't seen anything.
我们的无人机一直在上空监控
Our drones have been overhead the whole time.
他们什么也没发现
They saw nothing.
他在哪里
Where is he?
我们不知道
We don't know.
上去
Step up.